▶ Well, something is fishy...
▶ 수상한 것을 찾아보자

Output (Python 2.x):
출력 (파이썬 2.x):

Shouldn't that be 100?
답이 왜 100이 아닐까요?

Note: If you're not able to reproduce this, try running the file mixed_tabs_and_spaces.py via the shell.
정보: 복사-붙여넣기가 불가능하다면 shell에서 mixed_tabs_and_spaces.py 파일을 실행하세요.

💡 Explanation
💡 설명

Don't mix tabs and spaces! The character just preceding return is a "tab", and the code is indented by multiple of "4 spaces" elsewhere in the example.
탭과 공백을 섞어서 입력하지 마세요! 예시에서 볼 수 있듯 return 앞에 와야 할 문자는 탭이고, 코드는 4개의 공백으로 들여씁니다.

This is how Python handles tabs:
다음은 파이썬이 탭을 다루는 방법입니다.

First, tabs are replaced (from left to right) by one to eight spaces such that the total number of characters up to and including the replacement is a multiple of eight <...>
탭은 다음 문자까지의 총 문자 수가 8의 배수가 되도록 1개에서 8개 사이의 공백으로 대체됩니다.

So the "tab" at the last line of square function is replaced with eight spaces, and it gets into the loop.
square 함수의 마지막 줄에 들어가는 탭은 8개의 공백으로 대체되고, 무한루프를 유발합니다.

Python 3 is kind enough to throw an error for such cases automatically.
파이썬 3은 이러한 에러를 스스로 인식하여 알려줍니다.

Output (Python 3.x):
출력 (파이썬 3.x):