▶ Teleportation *
▶ 순간이동하는 *

Output:
출력:

Where's the Nobel Prize?
np는 어디 갔을까요?

💡 Explanation:
💡 설명

Notice that the numpy array created in the energy_send function is not returned, so that memory space is free to reallocate.
energy_send 함수에서 생성된 numpy 배열이 반환되지 않았기 때문에 재할당하는 데 필요한 메모리 공간이 충분합니다.

numpy.empty() returns the next free memory slot without reinitializing it. This memory spot just happens to be the same one that was just freed (usually, but not always).
numpy.empty()는 재할당 없이 비어있는 다음 메모리 공간을 반환합니다. 이 메모리 공간은 주로 직전에 할당 해제된 메모리 공간과 동일합니다.