Section: Appearances are deceptive!
섹션: 외모는 속임수에 불과합니다!

▶ Skipping lines?
▶ 줄 건너뛰기

Output:
출력:

Wut?
왜 위와 같은 결과가 나올까요?

Note: The easiest way to reproduce this is to simply copy the statements from the above snippet and paste them into your file/shell.
정보: 위 코드를 당신 컴퓨터의 shell에 복사-붙여넣기하면 가장 쉽게 따라칠 수 있습니다.

💡 Explanation
💡 설명

Some non-Western characters look identical to letters in the English alphabet but are considered distinct by the interpreter.
일부 서양문자는 영어 알파벳과 똑같이 생겼지만, 컴퓨터는 이들을 서로 다른 문자로 인식합니다.

The built-in ord() function returns a character's Unicode code point, and different code positions of Cyrillic 'e' and Latin 'e' justify the behavior of the above example.
내장된 ord() 함수는 문자의 유니코드를 반환하고, 키릴문자 'e'와 라틴문자 'e'의 서로 다른 코드는 위의 예제의 결과를 설명해줍니다.